Guide to the Billboard Photograph Collection ca 1918-1934 PR 5
New-York Historical Society
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60048)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60049)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60050)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60051)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60052)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60053)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60054)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60055)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60056)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60057)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 26, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60058)
- 6th Ave & 27th Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 26, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60059)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 26, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60060)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, August 26, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60061)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60062)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60063)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60064)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60065)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60066)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60067)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60068)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60069)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60070)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60071)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60072)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60073)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60074)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60075)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60076)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60077)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60078)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, October 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60079)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60080)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60081)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60082)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60083)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60084)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60085)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60086)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60087)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60088)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60089)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, November 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60090)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60091)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60092)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60093)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60094)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60095)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60096)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60097)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60098)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60099)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60100)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60101)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 28, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60102)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60103)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60104)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60105)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60106)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60107)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60108)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60109)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60110)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60111)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60112)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60113)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60114)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1927 (Box 11, Item 60115)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, January 27, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60116)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 27, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60117)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 27, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60118)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 27, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60119)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60120)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60121)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60122)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60123)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60124)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60125)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60126)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60127)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60128)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60129)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60130)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1928 (Box 11, Item 60131)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60132)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60133)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60134)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60135)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60136)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60137)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60138)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60139)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60140)
- 6th Ave & 47th, February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60141)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60142)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 26, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60143)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60144)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60145)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60146)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60147)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60148)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60149)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60150)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60151)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60152)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60153)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60154)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60155)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60156)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60157)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60158)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60159)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60160)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60161)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60162)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60163)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60164)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60165)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60166)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60167)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60168)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60169)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 28, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60170)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60171)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60172)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60173)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60174)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, June 29, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60175)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60176)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60177)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60178)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60179)
- 6th Ave & 27th, June 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60180)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60181)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60182)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 24, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60183)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Same as 60183; billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 24, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60183A)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 24, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60184)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 25, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60185)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 25, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60186)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 24, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60187)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 24, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60188)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 25, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60189)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 25, 1928 (Box 12, Item 60190)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 25, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60191)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 25, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60192)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, July 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60193)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60194)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60195)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60196)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60197)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60198)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60199)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 24, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60200)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60201)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60202)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60203)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60204)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60205)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60206)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60207)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60208)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60209)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60210)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60211)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60212)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60213)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60214)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60215)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60216)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60217)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60218)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 26, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60219)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60220)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, September 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60221)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60222)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60223)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60224)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60225)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60226)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60227)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60228)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, October 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60229)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60230)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60231)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60232)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60233)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60234)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60235)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60236)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60237)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60238)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60239)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60240)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60241)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60242)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60243)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 27, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60244)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60245)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60246)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60247)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60248)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60249)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60250)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60251)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60252)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1928 (Box 13, Item 60253)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 27, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60254)
- 6th Ave & 44th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60255)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60256)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60257)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60258)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60259)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60260)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60261)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60262)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60263)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 13, Item 60264)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 29, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60265)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 30, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60266)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 29, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60267)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 25, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60268)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 25, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60269)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 25, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60270)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60271)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60272)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60273)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60274)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60275)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60276)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 28, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60277)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 28, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60278)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 28, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60279)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 28, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60280)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards, February 28, 1929 (Box 14, Item 60281)
- 5th Ave & 42nd View along Fifth Avenue in front of the New York Public Library. No Billboards, August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60282)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60283)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60284)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60285)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60286)